[MARIELA] That devil-spawn father of yours
is together with Billy's aunt!
I'll kill them!
No one's dying, okay?
And most of all,
I don't want you to hurt yourself.
[MARIELA] I won't do it
ever again. [SOBS]
I regret doing it.
It's what caused your sister's death.
[BEA] Ma, you have to promise me
that you'll leave our revenge to me.
I will avenge us.
I will avenge us both, okay?
Good evening.
I'll just give you the latest update.
We're still looking for Mariela Mercado
and her daughter, Beatrice.
Authorities reported
no fatalities in the fire
that broke out at the home
of LoveList CEO Benilda Cariño.
Her father, Enrico Dominguez, however,
remains in a critical condition
after rescuing his son,
Oliver Cariño,
and a woman identified
as Oliver's guardian,
Precious Amador.
Did you hear what your father did?
Acting like a savior!
He went into the fire
to rescue his illegitimate child
and his mistress!
What about us?
What has he done for us?
Nothing!
[REPORTER] CCTV footage revealed
a woman entering the property
shortly before the fire started.
Police have identified her
as Mariela Mercado.
Mercado is now being sought by the police
and is considered a person of interest
in the investigation.
[MARIELA] Why should I be punished?
They're the ones who should suffer!
Not me!
Not us!
[BEA] You're Caloy's friend.
Wilfred, right?
You need a fake passport?
For my mom and me.
600,000.
That's too much, Bea!
I already gave you money.
I already gave you the files.
I did everything you asked me to do!
This is our new deal!
You give me 10 million pesos
cash tomorrow,
or our pictures,
your pictures, it will go viral.
So you choose.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
My big girl is 15 years old now.
Time sure flies, doesn't it?
Happy birthday, my dear.
Happy 18th birthday, my dear!
I can't believe you're 18 already.
I am so proud of you
and your company's success.
I hope LoveList will continue to prosper.
I'm here, cheering you on.
[POIGNANT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOFT FOOTSTEPS]
[PRECIOUS] Billy.
Did you get your father's medicine?
Yes.
What's that?
- [MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [PAPER RUSTLING]
Enrico's letters?
This is a lot.
Every…
Every Christmas,
graduation,
and birthday.
Oliver has some too, Aunt Precious.
He didn't forget
about us after all, Auntie.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[ECG MACHINE BEEPING STEADILY]
[ENRICO GRUNTS]
[ENRICO] Dear.
Are you safe?
Dad.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
How do you feel?
[ECG MACHINE BEEPING]
Thank you, my dear.
Thank you for the opportunity you gave me
to be with your brother.
Thank you for saving Oliver
and Auntie Pres, Dad.
How are they?
They're going to be fine.
Don't worry.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
I saw that you smiled at your father.
You know, it is a big deal for him.
What he did was no joke,
saving you and Oliver.
My father almost died because
of the fire, Auntie Pres.
That's too much.
[PHONE RINGING]
Jordan?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hello?
[JORDAN] Dude?
I'm here at your house.
They've recovered some of your things.
Would you like to see?
Okay.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
MIDNIGHT, OKAY? OR ELSE.
How long are we staying here?
Um…
Not long.
We're going to get out of here soon.
How?
[EXHALES SHARPLY] Ma.
I'm making a way, okay?
I'll take care of it. I told you, right?
I won't let you go to jail.
I-I'm sorry, dear.
I've become even more of a burden to you.
Ma. You're my mother.
Okay?
You'll never be a burden to me.
You're the only family I have.
I'd do anything for you.
I'm not.
You still have a father.
The thing is,
we're not important to him anymore.
Is that jerk still alive?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello, Daddy? Yes, I'm on my way.
Are you all right?
Okay, okay.
Bye.
Oh, there.
Your fever has gone down a bit.
But don't leave me yet, Pa.
You might leave again.
Of course I won't leave my baby.
Not until I'm sure that you're all better.
- [LAUGHS]
- [SIGHS CONTENTEDLY]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[ELEVATOR DOOR OPENS]
Initially, the medical team thought
diabetes was your preexisting condition.
But upon further evaluation
of your condition,
you are in an advanced stage
of heart failure.
And based on your medical records,
you have maintenance medicines
needed for this.
But, Enrico, this is not enough.
[ECG MACHINE BEEPING]
Doc, have you told my family?
Ah, not yet.
Doc, please.
Don't tell them.
Your family needs to know
that you have arteries that are blocked.
Enrico, you will have to
tell them sooner or later.
You'll need surgery.
That will require a lot of money.
I can't afford that, Doc.
I don't want to be a burden to them.
Well, we don't want
your heart to get overworked,
so I suggest you get some rest.
Let's talk about the procedure tomorrow.
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING]
[NURSE] This is for the chest pain.
This will make you a bit drowsy, okay?
[ECG MACHINE BEEPING]
[DOCTOR] Okay.
I'll see you tomorrow, Enrico.
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
You know, since I already
invested my money,
let's just do it.
Come hell or high water,
we will launch LoveLine.
How?
You no longer have an investor.
I'll pawn the house. Double mortgage!
[FLICKS] You're nuts!
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What do they say is the best school?
It's there in California!
The University of Kingsley.
That's the best school
for software engineering!
- Hmm!
- But…
It's too expensive.
I could study here too.
There are also many Philippine schools
that offer software engineering.
I have my top three schools I can go to.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
University of Kingsley.
Noted. Okay, you'll study here.
- Really, Billy?
- Mm-hmm!
- Sure?
- Promise?
- Promise.
I'm going to study well,
so your efforts won't go to waste.
When I graduate,
you can stop working,
so you can finally rest.
You know I'd do anything for you, right?
That's okay.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Don't worry, Billy.
We'll protect each other.
Always.
Oh, enough with the flattery.
- Just help me instead.
- You want that?
You want a hug?
- Sure, hug this.
- Okay.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOFT THUD]
- [SNIFFLES]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC TURNS SUSPENSEFUL]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Pa?
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
- Pa!
- Hey.
Mm.
A brand-new car?
Is that ours?
Yes.
Now we can go on as many trips as we want.
You miss your sister, don't you?
Well, now we have a car
to visit her in Manila.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Manila?
So when are we leaving?
Today!
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
We're going right now?
- Yes, so let's go!
- [STAMMERS]
- Your mother's all dressed up.
- Yeah, she is!
Oh! Okay, I won't bother changing then!
- Here, I brought some clothes.
- Let me help you.
Oh, really? Thanks, Ma!
Oh…
- Ma?
- Hmm?
- Can I take the front seat?
- Nuh-uh.
- You can't.
- Okay then.
You can sit there.
[MARIELA GRUNTS]
Okay?
[ENGINE STARTS]
- Let's go!
- Ready?
- We're ready!
- Where do you want to go?
First stop.
A convenience store.
- Convenience store! Let's go!
- My goodness…
[MONITOR BEEPING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Did you hear what your father did?
Acting like a savior!
He went into the fire
to rescue his illegitimate child
and his mistress!
What about us?
What has he done for us?
Nothing!
[MONITOR BEEPING]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BEA] What Mama did was wrong.
It's your fault she turned out like this.
Because you hurt her.
Left her.
You ruined Mama's life.
Our life.
But I'm also mad at myself.
Because I shouldn't be worried about you.
I shouldn't.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MONITOR BEEPING]
Miss.
We'll do a partial payment.
Billy, you should take this too.
- Here, take it.
- No need, Auntie.
I'll take care of it as long as I can.
[CASHIER] I'm sorry, ma'am.
Your card was declined.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[PRECIOUS] Billy…
Okay, miss. Just a minute.
I have another card.
I'll just get it from upstairs.
[BILLY] Let's go.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ELEVATOR RINGS]
[PRECIOUS] Billy? Billy, wait!
- Billy! Billy!
- Bea!
- [PRECIOUS] Nurse!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Billy! Billy!
- Hey, let go of me! Hey!
- How dare you show up here?!
- [GROANS]
Why?! You want to make sure
that we're dead, huh?!
What are you talking about?!
- I'm not an idiot!
- [SLAPS]
Your mother's face was seen clearly
on the CCTV footage.
And you're blaming me
for what happened?
Every single bad thing
going on in your life,
you'll blame on-- [GROANS]
We almost died because of you.
[VOICE BREAKING] My father
almost died because of you!
[CHUCKLES] That's karma!
- Karma!
- You witch!
- [PRECIOUS] Billy…
- You bastard!
Billy, that's enough. Enough!
- It's because of you!
- Enough, Billy!
Billy!
[PANTING HEAVILY]
Billy, that's enough! Billy!
Guard!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[BILLY] Where do you think you're going?
- Damn you!
- [BEA GRUNTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[BEA SCREAMING]
Get off me!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
[BILLY] What, huh?!
You and your mother will pay.
It'll be jail time for you.
- [SCREAMS]
- What more do you want from me, huh?!
Miss, get me away from her.
See? She's getting closer.
She'll punch me again.
She did this to me.
Get her away from me.
I overlooked her
being released many times.
But who knows? Arson might not be
all she'll do next time.
She might just murder us.
- Tell Billy your true feelings.
- I don't want to add to her problems.
[BILLY] I need your help.
I'm tired of getting my hopes
up for nothing.
Your and your mom's passports
and birth certificates are ready. Here.
Pack your things. We're leaving.
We're going to Taiwan.
You accept that you lost
to your father's illegitimate daughter?
If they put you in jail,
that's when we lose!
I'm at the lobby. Meet me here.
Delete the photo once you get the money,
and then don't ever bother me again!
[BILLY] I'll put a stop to them myself.
[JORDAN] This can't be a coincidence.
This is where I traced the location
of the person who leaked LoveList's files.